This kitty is Mittens. This one is Fitzhugh.
這隻小貓叫手套 這只是費修
And this little guy in the cat condo is Jinkies.
然後這住在貓公寓的小男生是金吉
That's a lot of cats, Jo Lynn.
好多貓喔，裘琳
Single, are you?
你是單身吧？
- I'll get it. - Okay.
-我來接 -好啊！
Chandler Bing.
錢德賓
How come you're answering your own phone? Where's your crazy assistant?
為什麼你是自己接電話呢？ 你的瘋狂助理去哪了？
You're not crazy. You're not crazy.
你沒有瘋，你沒有瘋
Otherwise, why would you have all those cats?
否則你怎麼會養那麼多隻貓呢？
What's up, Joe?
什麼事，喬伊？
What have we always wanted to do together?
有什麼事是我們一直想要一起做的？
Braid each other's hair and ride horseback on the beach?
幫彼此編辮子然後在海邊騎馬嗎？
No. No. No. When you get home tomorrow night..
不不不，你明晚回家時…
you and I are gonna be at the Wizards-Knicks game, courtside!
你跟我要去看巫師隊對尼克隊球賽 場邊座位！
- Courtside? Oh, my God! - Yeah!
-場邊座位？喔！我的天啊！ -是啊！
Maybe Michael Jordan will dive for the ball and break my jaw with his knee!
或許麥可喬登會撲過來搶球 然後用他的膝蓋撞斷我的下巴！
That is so cool. I'll let Monica know.
真是太酷了，我來告訴摩妮卡
These need your signature.
這些需要你的簽名
Listen, Jo Lynn, that was my friend Joey. He calls everybody crazy.
聽著，裘琳，那是我朋友喬伊 他總是叫每個人瘋狂的
- Hello? - Hey, hon, it's me.
-哈囉？ -嘿，親愛的，是我
Hi. How's the crazy cat lady?
嘿，那個瘋狂貓女人還好嗎？
Joey just called.
喬伊剛打電話來…
He's got courtside Knicks tickets for him and me tomorrow night.
他幫我買到了明晚 尼克隊比賽的場邊座位
But tomorrow night's the only night I get off from the restaurant.
但是明晚是我唯一不用上班的晚上
If you go, we won't have a night together for a week.
如果你去看球賽 我們會有一星期沒有辦法在一起
But honey, it's courtside! The cheerleaders will be right in..
但是親愛的，那是場邊座位！ 啦啦隊會就在正前…
That's not the way to convince you.
這不是說服你的好方式
I don't wanna be one of those wives that says:
我不想要成為那種老婆 老是說：
"You can't go to the game. You have to spend time with me."
「你不能去看球賽，你要陪我」
So if you could just realize it on your own..
所以如果你自己能夠有認知…
I know. You're right. I wanna see you too.
我知道，你說的對 我也想要見到你
I gotta figure out a way to tell Joey. He's looking forward to it.
我得要想想要怎麼告訴喬伊 他是滿心期待著
Tell him you haven't seen your wife in a long time.
告訴他你很久沒有見到老婆了
Tell him that having a long-distance relationship is really difficult.
告訴他長距離關係是很難維繫的
Tell him that what little time we have together is precious.
告訴他 我們這些有限的相處時間是很寶貴的
I'll think of something.
我會想想別的
The One With Rachel's Phone Number
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
You look..
你看起來…
I mean, it's just.. That dress..
我是說，這真的… 這件洋裝…
Well, I hope the ends of these sentences are good.
嗯，我希望那句話的結尾是正面的
They're good. It's just been a while since I've seen you like this.
是好的，只是我很久沒有 看到你這樣打扮
You clean up good.
你產後恢復的真好
Really? Well, thank you.
真的嗎？ 喔，謝謝你
Okay, stop looking at me like that.
好了，別再這樣看著我了
- Last time that happened, that happened. - Right, right.
-上次這樣的時候，就那樣了 -對，是的
So are you excited about your first night away from Emma?
你很高興你第一次可以離開艾□ 晚上出去玩嗎？
Yeah, yeah. Phoebe and l are gonna have so much fun.
是啊，菲比跟我會玩的很開心的
- Thank you for watching the baby. - It's fine.
-謝謝你幫我看小孩 -不用客氣
Actually, I invited Mike over.
事實上，我有邀請麥克過來
- Phoebe's Mike? - Yeah.
-菲比的麥克嗎？ -是啊
- I didn't know you hung out. - We don't..
-我不知道你們很熟 -我們沒有…
but I'd like to get to know him.
但是我想要多認識他
Maybe have a little dinner, drinks, conversation.
或許用點晚餐，喝點酒然後聊聊天
That's so cute. Ross and Mike's first date.
好純真可愛 羅斯跟麥克的第一次約會
It's not a date.
這不是約會
But if it turns out to be something more..
但是如果發展成更進一步的關係…
I'll leave a tie on the door.
我會在門把上綁帶子
Will that be awkward? What are you gonna talk about?
那會不會很尷尬呢？ 你們要聊些什麼呢？
I don't know. But you know, we have a lot in common, you know?
我不知道，但是你知道的 我們有許多共同點，你知道嗎？
He plays piano. I played keyboards in college.
他會彈鋼琴，我在大學彈過鍵盤
He's been divorced. I have some experience in that area.
他離過婚，我在那方面也有些經驗
- Yeah? - Hi!
-是嗎？ -嗨！
Girl's night out indeed.
果真是女人之夜
So I think Emma is probably down for the night..
我想艾□今晚可能已經睡了…
- but if you need anything.. - We'll be fine.
-但是如果你們需要… -我們會沒事的
- You go have fun. - Okay, you too.
-祝你們玩得愉快 -好的，你們也是
- Thanks. - And I hope you score.
-謝謝 -還有我希望你可以上壘得分
- Okay. Bye. - Bye.
-好的，再見 -再見
So, welcome.
嗯，歡迎
- I got beer. - I got bottled breast milk.
-我有啤酒 -我有瓶裝母乳
- Why don't we start with the beer. - Okay.
-我看我們先喝啤酒好了 -好的
- So Phoebe tells me you play piano. - Yeah.
-菲比告訴我你會彈鋼琴 -是啊
You know, I used to play keyboards in college.
我在大學的時候也會彈鍵盤
Do you have one here?
你這裡有嗎？
No.
沒有
Okay.
好的
You know, I'm divorced.
你知道的，我離過婚…
Phoebe.. Phoebe says you're.. You've been divorced?
菲比…菲比…說你… 你也離過婚？
Yeah, yeah.
是的，是啊
Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't really like to talk about it.
很抱歉，我真的不太喜歡談那件事
That's okay. We'll talk about something else.
沒關係，我們可以聊別的
- This is a nice apartment. - Thanks.
-這間公寓蠻不錯的 -謝謝
The moldings are all original.
這些裝飾條板都是原來就有的
I don't know if the moldings are original in my apartment.
我不知道我公寓的裝飾條板 是不是原創的？
- So you're a paleontologist, right? - Yeah.
-你是古生物學家，是嗎？ -是啊
My cousin's a paleontologist.
我表哥也是古生物學家
Well, he and I would probably have a lot to talk about.
嗯，他跟我可能會有較多話題可以聊
- Welcome home. - Well, look at you.
-歡迎回家 -嗯，瞧瞧你
Yeah. What do you think?
是啊，覺得怎樣呢？
Well, it looks great. It's just..
嗯，看起來很棒，只不過…
I'm wearing the same thing underneath, so..
我裡面穿的也跟你一樣，所以…
You see what I mean?
你知道我的意思嗎？
Hey! How come your door's locked?
嘿！為什麼你的門是鎖著的？
- Just a second! - No, no, no!
-等一下！ -不不不！
- Joey can't know I'm here. - Why not?
-喬伊不能看到我在這裡 -為什麼不能？
I didn't want to say I couldn't go to the game..
我不知道怎麼告訴他 我不能去看球賽…
- so I told him I had to stay in Tulsa. - So you lied to him?
-所以我跟他說我得要留在土爾沙 -所以你跟他說謊？
It's always better to lie than to have the complicated discussion.
說謊比費口舌解釋要好太多了
Except with you.
除了跟你之外
Hey, open the door! What's going on?
嘿，開門！是怎麼回事？
- What are you..? - Hi.
-你是在幹麼？ -嗨
Why are you dressed like that?
你為什麼穿成這樣呢？
Because Chandler's gonna be home in a couple of days..
因為錢德幾天以後就要回來了…
so I thought I would just, you know, practice the art of seduction.
所以我想可以 先練習一下嫵媚的技巧
I thought I heard a man's voice before.
我剛剛好像有聽到男人的聲音
No, I was just doing Chandler's side of the conversation.
沒有，我只是在扮演錢德說話
You know, like, "Hi, how do I look?"
你知道的，就像是： 「嗨，我看起來如何？」
"Really sexy. Could I be any more turned on?" You know?
「真性感，我還能比現在更興奮嗎？」 你知道的
Okay. Wait a minute.
好的，等一下
Why are there two glasses of wine out?
為什麼有兩杯酒呢？
Because one of them is for you!
因為一杯是要給你的
Cheers! Okay, bye-bye.
乾杯！好了，再見
You know, it's funny. I've been practicing the art of seduction myself.
真好玩，我自己也一直 在練習勾引的技巧
- You might wanna keep practicing. - Yeah.
-你最好再繼續加強練習 -是喔！
- It's Joey. - What?
-是喬伊 -什麼？
- Hey, Joe. - Dude, come home!
-嘿，喬伊 -老兄，回家！
- What? Why? - Come home!
-什麼？為什麼？ -回家！
Look, I can't. What's going on?
聽著，我不行，是怎麼回事呢？
I don't know how to tell you this, but I think Monica's cheating on you!
我不知道要怎麼開口 但是我想摩妮卡背著你劈腿！
I told you, you shouldn't have married someone hotter than you!
早就告訴過你，你不應該娶一個 比你辣那麼多的人！
If you can't deal with this, then I'm gonna.
如果你沒有辦法回來處理這種事 那我去處理
- No! - I just heard him!
-不！ -我聽到他的聲音了！
Can you hear him now?
你現在有聽到他的聲音嗎？
No. All right, I'm going in.
沒有，好了，我要進去了
- No, wait! - I heard him again!
-不，等等！ -我又聽到他了！
All right, just stay there. I'm coming home.
好了，你就待在那裡別動 我要回家了
I'll see you when you get here.
等你回來的時候見
I'll wait out in the hall in case he comes out.
我會在門外守著以免他走了
- Is that really necessary? - Absolutely. You'd do it for me.
-有那個必要嗎？ -當然，你也會為我這樣做的
Not that you ever have to, because I know how to keep my women satisfied.
不是說你會有機會那樣做 因為我知道要如何滿足我的女人
- Yeah, listen, thanks a lot. - Okay, bye.
-是啊，聽著，萬分感謝 -好了，再見
He thinks I'm a slut.
他認為我是淫蕩的女人
Oh, right, and you're supposed to be a fireman?
喔，對了 你不是應該當義勇消防隊員的嗎？
Shouldn't the pizza be here by now?
披薩不是早就該到了嗎？
I mean, they said 30 minutes or less. Well, how long has it been?
我是說，他們說不用三十分鐘就會到 已經多久了呢？
Eleven minutes.
十一分鐘
And now 12.
現在是十二分鐘
- So you wanna watch TV? - You think I haven't thought of that?
-那你想看電視嗎？ -你以為我沒有想過嗎？
I mean, I would like to but the cable's out.
我也想啊，但是第四台斷了
Didn't seem like such a big deal until tonight.
本來不覺得有什麼大不了的，直到今晚
- So you like the beer? - I do. I do.
-你喜歡這啤酒嗎？ -是的，我喜歡
Although, it's actually a lager.
不過，這事實上是淡啤酒
What's the difference between beer and lager?
那啤酒跟淡啤酒有什麼不同呢？
I don't know.
我不知道
We could look it up.
我們可以查一查
Things are about to get wild.
真是越來越有趣了
Oh, God, remember the girls' nights we used to have..
喔，天啊 還記得以前的女生之夜我們…
sitting around talking about you and Ross?
坐在一起討論你跟羅斯的事嗎？
Oh, God! It seems like forever ago.
喔！天啊！感覺好像是上輩子的事
I know.
我知道
So, what's going on with you and Ross?
那，你跟羅斯是怎樣了呢？
Well, I don't know. I mean, for a long time, nothing.
喔，我不知道，我是說 已經很久沒有怎樣了
But you know, actually, right before you picked me up..
但是，事實上 就在你來接我之前…
Ross and I had a little thing.
羅斯跟我有個小小的「插曲」
Oh, my God! I love things! What happened?
喔！我的天！我最愛小插曲！ 發生什麼事？
Well, first he told me he liked how I looked.
嗯，他先是告訴我 他喜歡我看起來的樣子
And then we had a little..
然後我們做了個小小的…
eye contact.
眼神交換
Eye contact?
眼神交換？
I hope you were using protection.
我希望你們有用避孕措施
Excuse me, these are from the two gentlemen at the end of the bar.
不好意思 這些是吧檯最後那兩位先生請的
Oh, actually, I can't have another one on account of my breast milk.
喔，事實上 因為餵母乳的關係我不能多喝一杯
Okay.
好的
Hey, Rach, maybe there's a less disgusting way to decline a drink.
嘿，瑞秋，有沒有比較不噁心的理由 可以讓你不喝酒的
Should we send them something back? Let's send them mashed potatoes!
我們應該回請他們什麼嗎？ 我們請他們吃馬鈴薯泥好了！
No, wait! Don't do that!
不，等等！別那麼做！
That'll make them think they can come over.
那樣他們就會認為他們可以過來
So, what if they do?
所以呢？過來又如何呢？
We're not here to meet guys. You have a boyfriend. I have a baby and a Ross.
我們不是來這裡釣男人的 你有男友，我有小孩還有羅斯
Yeah, but nothing has to happen. We're just having fun.
是啊，但這只是好玩 又不會發生什麼事
You know, not everything has to go as far as eye contact.
你知道的 不是每件事都得發展到眼神交換地步的
Chandler, you have to tell Joey you're not in Tulsa.
錢德，你得要告訴喬伊你不在土爾沙
Isn't it better for him to think you're cheating on me..
讓他認為是你在欺騙我…
than for him to think I'm cheating on him?
總比他認為我在欺騙他好吧？
I heard it.
我自己聽到了
I don't want him to think I'm having an affair.
我不想讓他誤會我有外遇
All right, I've got a plan. I'll go down the fire escape..
好了，我有個計劃 我會從防火梯爬下去…
Because all good plans start with, "I'll go down the fire escape."
所有完美的計劃都是從 「我會從防火梯爬下去」開始的
Hear me out, woman!
聽我說完，女人！
I'll go down the fire escape and wait.
我會從防火梯爬下去然後等著
Then it'll be like I just got back from Tulsa.
然後就會像是我剛從土爾沙回來一樣…
Joey and I will come in and see that there's no guy in here.
然後喬伊跟我進來 看到這裡根本沒有男人
Aren't you afraid that Joey's gonna figure all this out?
你難道不怕喬伊會識破嗎？
I heard it.
我自己聽到了
- I'm gonna wait. - The scary pigeon's back?
-我要等一下 -可怕的鴿子又回來了嗎？
It's huge.
超大的
I can't believe you live in that building. My grandmother lives in that building!
我不敢相信你住在那棟公寓 我奶奶也住在那棟公寓！
Ida Greene? No sense of personal space..
艾達葛林，沒有個人空間感…
kind of smells like chicken, looks like a potato.
聞起來像雞，看起來像馬鈴薯
- "Spuds" is your grandmother? - That's my bubbe!
-「洋芋」是你奶奶？ -那就是我「啊嬤」！
So we're on our way to a couple of parties.
我們要再去幾個派對
Maybe we could get your numbers and call if we find something fun?
或許我們可以跟你們要號碼 如果遇到好玩的，打電話給你們
Yeah. I'm sorry, we weren't really looking for anything to happen..
我很抱歉，我們並沒有在找什麼對像
with you guys. I have a boyfriend.
我有男朋友了
- All right. - It's no big deal.
-好的 -沒關係
Just out of curiosity, which one of you was for me?
只是好奇，你們哪一個喜歡我呢？
- That would've been me. - Nice.
-是我 -很好
Different situation, cowboy, and you would've had yourself a handful.
如果情況不同，小子 你可是會有得忙的
So she has a boyfriend. What is your situation?
所以她有男朋友 那你的情形是怎樣呢？
Well, it's complicated. I don't actually have a boyfriend, but..
嗯，這有點複雜 我並沒有男朋友，但是…
Then can I have your number?
那我可以跟你要電話號碼嗎？
I'm sorry, no.
我很抱歉，不行
Okay.
好的
Oh, sure!
喔，當然可以！
Oh, my God, you're giving your real number!
喔！天啊，你給他的電話是真的！
Okay, thanks. I'll give you a call later tonight.
好的，謝謝，我今晚會打給你
- Great. - Bye.
-太好了 -再見
Bye.
再見
So that's great.
那真的太棒了
You, Bill, Ross and Emma are gonna be so happy together.
你、比爾、羅斯、還有艾□ 會很快樂在一起
What were you thinking?
你是在想什麼呢？
I don't know. He was cute, and he liked me. It was an impulse.
我不知道，他很可愛然後又喜歡我 我衝動之下就給他了
Like when I bought these shoes. They were cute and they liked me too.
就像我買這雙鞋的時候 它們很可愛而且也喜歡我
But what about Ross? What about your moment?
那羅斯怎麼辦嗎？你們的小插曲呢？
We had a moment. We looked at each other.
我們是有過小插曲 我們對看了彼此
Maybe if we live together for another 10 years, we may hold hands!
或許如果我們一起住了十年 我們可能就會牽手了！
But you were really excited about it.
但是你原本對這件事 是非常高興的
- Don't you wanna talk to him? - No.
-你不想要跟他談嗎？ -不想
No, because I know exactly how the conversation's gonna go.
不想，因為我完全知道 談話的結果會是怎樣
"Hey, Ross, you know, I think we had a moment before."
「嘿！羅斯，我認為我們 剛剛有個小插曲」
"Yeah. Me too."
「是啊，我也這麼認為」
"Well, but I'm not sure I really want to do anything about it."
「嗯，但是我不太確定 我是不是想再更進一步」
"Yeah. Me neither."
「是啊，我也不確定」
"Should we just live together..
我們是不是就住在一起…
and not tell each other how we're feeling?"
然後不要告訴彼此 我們互相的感受？
"Yeah, that works for me."
「是啊，我沒意見」
Yeah, I see what you mean.
是啊，我知道你的意思
By the way, nice Ross imitation.
對了，你模仿的羅斯真像
Your Rachel wasn't whiny enough.
你模仿的瑞秋 不夠愛發牢騷
- Well.. Hey! - Better.
-嗯…嘿！ -好多了
The point is maybe I should just stop waiting around for moments with Ross.
重點是我或許應該停止等待 跟羅斯之間的小插曲
You know? I should just move on with my life.
你知道嗎？我應該要過我自己的生活了
So really, you're moving on from Ross?
真的，你要放棄羅斯了？
I don't know. Do I have to decide right now?
我不知道，我得要現在做決定嗎？
You kind of just did. That guy is gonna call you tonight.
你好像已經做了 那男的今晚會打電話給你
Ross will pick up the phone, and that's a pretty clear message.
羅斯會接起電話，這是挺明白的訊息了
Oh, my God, Ross!
喔！天啊，羅斯！
Ross is gonna pick up the phone.
羅斯會接起電話
I have to get my number back. Oh, my God, he's gone!
我得拿回我的電話號碼 喔！天啊，他走了！
"Oh, I have to get my number back! Oh, my God! He's gone!" Dead on.
「我得拿回我的電話號碼 喔！天啊，他走了！」模仿的真棒
- You know, I'm gonna take off. - So soon?
-我想我該走了 -這麼快嗎？
- Yeah. - Okay.
-是啊 -好的
Well, thanks.. Thanks for the beer.
嗯，謝謝你帶啤酒過來
- You mean lager? - Yeah. Good times.
-你是說淡啤酒吧？ -是啊，快樂時光
- Okay. - All right.
-好的 -好了
- Hello? - Hey, Mike, it's me.
-哈囉？ -嘿，麥克，是我
Listen, is.. Is Ross near you?
聽著，羅斯在你旁邊嗎？
No, I just left.
沒有，我才剛走
And that, right there, is the most interesting conversation I've had all night.
而現在，是我今晚 有過最有趣的對話了
Really? Okay.
真的嗎？好的
Well, you have to go back in.
嗯，你得要再回去
What? Go back? To the land where time stands still?
什麼？回去？回到時光暫停之地嗎？
I'm so sorry, honey, but..
我很抱歉，親愛的，但是…
Okay, Rachel gave this guy her number..
瑞秋給了一個男的她的電話…
and she doesn't want Ross to answer the phone.
她不希望羅斯去接電話
So you have to intercept all his calls.
所以你必須要攔截他所有的電話
I can't do that!
我不能這樣做！
- He says he can't do that. - Give me the phone.
-他說他不能那樣做 -電話給我
Hi, Mike. Hi, listen, I know that this is a lot to ask, but you know what?
麥克，聽著，我知道這個要求很過分 但是你知道嗎？
If you do this, Phoebe will do anything you want.
如果你照做 菲比會做一切你想要她做的事
- Seriously, I'm talking dirty stuff. - All right. Thank you. Hello?
-真的，我說得是很下流的事 -好了，謝謝，哈囉？
Hi, I'm sorry about her. But actually, she wasn't wrong about the dirty stuff.
嗨，我替她道歉，但事實上 關於下流的事，她說的沒錯
All right, I'll do it.
好了，我照做
But really, how much dirtier can it get?
但說真的，會有多下流呢？
Oh, Mike.
喔，麥克
Bye.
拜拜
Hey, buddy.
嘿，老兄
Hi.
嗨
- Can I come back in? - Why?
-我可以回來嗎？ -為什麼？
Well, I was just thinking about how much more we have to talk about.
嗯，我只是在想我們 還有很多東西可以聊
But you left.
但是你走了
That didn't take long.
那倒是挺快的
I thought you said Tulsa was, like, a three-hour flight?
我以為你說土爾沙到這裡要飛三小時
Well, you're forgetting about the time difference.
嗯，你忘了把時差算進去了
- You ready? I'm gonna go in there with you. - Thanks.
-你準備好了嗎？我跟你一起進去 -謝謝
Just in case there's more than one dude in there.
以防裡面不只有一個男的
- Again, thanks. - Yeah.
-再一次謝謝你 -是啊
Chandler, you're home!
錢德，你回來了！
That's right! Your husband's home! So now the sex can stop!
沒錯！你老公回來了！ 所以現在性愛派對可以停止了！
You know what I mean.
你知道我在說什麼
What are you saying?
你是在說什麼？
Joey said you're here with another man!
喬伊說你跟另一個男人在一起！
There's no man in here! How dare you accuse me of that!
這裡根本沒有男人！ 你怎麼敢這樣誣賴我！
All right. Then maybe you won't mind if me and my friend take a look around.
好了，那或許你不介意 我和我的「朋友」到處看看
He can't even see us!
他根本搞不清楚狀況！
- I kind of liked it. - Me too.
-我蠻喜歡這樣的 -我也是
What's he doing?
他在做什麼？
I arranged some pillows on the bed to look like a guy.
我用枕頭做成人形在床上
Bedroom's clear. Although you might need some new pillows.
臥室沒有人 不過你們可能需要換新的枕頭了
All right, well, I'll check the guest room.
好了，那我去檢查客房
Why do I smell men's cologne?
我為什麼有聞到男人的古龍水味？
I think that's you.
我想那是你的味道
Oh, yeah. I rubbed a magazine on myself earlier.
喔，對喔，我剛剛才用 雜誌磨擦到自己身上
There's nobody here, Joe.
裡面沒有人，喬伊
I guess not.
我想也沒有
I can't believe you thought I was cheating. You owe me an apology.
我不敢相信你認為我會劈腿 你要對我道歉
- You're right. I'm so sorry. - It's an honest mistake.
-你說的對，我很抱歉 -這是出自好意的誤會
It could happen to anybody. See you.
可能發生在任何人身上的，再見
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
等一下，等一下
If you just got back from Tulsa, how did your suitcase beat you here?
如果你才剛從土爾沙回來 你的行李怎麼會比你先到？
I climbed down the fire escape, and you can't put that in the closet?
我從防火梯爬了下去 而你就不能把這個藏到衣櫥裡嗎？
So, with the exception of the fermentation process..
所以，除了發酵過程不同之外…
beer and ale are basically the same thing.
啤酒跟麥酒基本上是相同的東西
Fascinating, isn't it?
真引人入勝，不是嗎？
Maybe you should look up "fascinating."
或許你應該查一下「引人入勝」
I'll get it!
我來接！
Hello? Ross' place. Mike speaking.
哈囉？羅斯家，我是麥克
It's for you.
要找你的
I don't understand what just happened here.
我不懂剛剛發生的事
What's going on?
是怎麼回事？
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I told you I was in Tulsa because I wanted to spend the night with Monica..
我會跟你說我在土爾沙是因為 今晚我想要跟摩妮卡在一起…
and I didn't know.. I didn't think you'd understand.
而我不知道… 我以為你會不諒解
You think I'm too dumb to understand a husband needs to be with his wife?
你以為我笨到會不諒解 老公想要跟老婆在一起嗎？
You think I'm, like..
你以為我就像…
- Joey? - Yeah.
-喬伊？ -怎樣
I don't know what to say. We shouldn't have lied to you.
我不知道該說什麼 我們不應該欺騙你的
I feel so bad. Is there anything I can do to make it up to you?
我覺得很難過，我能做什麼補償你嗎？
You could go to the game with me. Even though you said you couldn't.
你可以跟我一起去看球賽 雖然你說了你不行
But then you lied to me and tricked me and gave me a bump on the head.
但是你欺騙我 然後又害我頭腫了一包
I'm sorry, that's the one thing I can't do. I promised I'd be with Monica.
我很抱歉，這是我唯一無法做到的 我答應摩妮卡要跟她在一起了
All right.
好吧
- You can go. - What?
-你去吧 -什麼？
You should go to the game. It's okay. I want you to.
你應該去看球賽，沒關係，我要你去
- Really? You gonna be okay? - Yeah, I'll be fine.
-真的？你沒關係嗎？ -是的，我沒關係
You know, maybe I'll stay here and practice the art of seduction.
你知道的，或許我可以留在這裡 然後練習一下勾引的技巧
- You're gonna put sweats on and clean. - It's gonna be so hot!
-你要換上運動服然後打掃吧 -一定會很性感撩人！
- Bye. - Bye.
-拜 -拜
Thanks.
謝了
Here's your ticket.
你的外套拿去
Thanks. Hey, listen..
謝了，嘿，聽著…
I'm never gonna lie to you again, okay?
我再也不會跟你說謊了，好嗎？
And I want you to know that nobody thinks you're stupid.
而且我要你知道沒有人認為你是愚蠢的
Thanks, man.
謝了，老兄
- Where you going? - Game's tomorrow night, Joe.
-你要去哪？ -球賽是明晚，喬伊
I'm glad I got to talk to your mom. She sounds nice.
我很高興跟你媽說到話 她聽起來人不錯
Yeah, she's a peach.
是啊，她人很好
Oh, God!
喔！天啊！
So glad you're back!
真高興你們回來了！
So, what did you guys do?
那你們做了些什麼呢？
You know, we just drank some beer.
你知道的，我們喝了一些啤酒
Mike played with the boundaries of normal social conduct.
麥克示範了正常社交禮儀的界線在哪
It's true, I did.
是真的，我做得很好
- Well, goodbye. - Okay.
-好了，再見 -好的
- Bye. That was fun, Phoebe. - I know. It was fun.
-拜，真好玩，菲比 -我知道，真好玩
See you, guys.
再見！
Lock the door! Lock the door, seriously.
鎖門！鎖門，快點
Shoot, I forgot to pay Phoebe for the drinks.
糟了，我忘記給菲比酒錢了
Wait, wait. Wait, sorry. Did he call? Did that guy call?
等等，等一下，不好意思 他有打來嗎？那個男的有打來嗎？
No, just his mom.
沒有，只有他媽打來
Around 8:30?
在八點半左右嗎？
- Yeah. - Then again at 9:00?
-是的 -然後九點再一通嗎？
Yeah.
是的
Hello?
哈囉？
No, she's not here right now. Can I take a message?
她現在不在，要留言嗎？
Bill from the bar?
酒吧認識的比爾？
Okay, Bill from the bar, I'll make sure she gets your number.
好的，酒吧認識的比爾 我會把你的號碼給她的
So.. So how was it?
好玩嗎？
Did you guys..? You guys have a good time?
你們有…？ 你們玩的開心嗎？
We had so much fun. It felt so good to be out.
我們玩的很開心，出去玩真是快樂
Rach?
瑞秋？
Yeah?
什麼事呢？
Never mind.
沒事
- Hey, you guys. - Hey!
-嗨，你們 -嘿！
I'll be right back. I gotta go to the bathroom.
馬上回來，我要去上廁所
Stout. That's a kind of beer.
黑啤酒也是啤酒的一種